[
    {
        "question": "The child's parents or ............ must give their agreement before she has the operation.",
        "choices": [
            "designers",
            "guardians",
            "donors",
            "monitors"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "guardians"
    },
    {
        "question": "Families should ............ their children's internet activity.",
        "choices": [
            "meet",
            "dick",
            "monitor",
            "scam"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "monitor"
    },
    {
        "question": "The police managed to ............ down the criminal.",
        "choices": [
            "track",
            "tick",
            "trek",
            "truck"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "track"
    },
    {
        "question": "The international ............ is really very worried about the problem of climate change.",
        "choices": [
            "security",
            "communication",
            "technology",
            "community"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "community"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Farmers keep livestock on their farms.\" The synonym of \"livestock\" is ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "kittle",
            "castle",
            "cattle",
            "kettle"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "cattle"
    },
    {
        "question": "The farmers build fences to protect their ............ from wild animals and thieves.",
        "choices": [
            "wildlife",
            "livestock",
            "parties",
            "tracks"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "livestock"
    },
    {
        "question": "He joined the tourist ............ who visited the Valley of Kings.",
        "choices": [
            "herd",
            "party",
            "flock",
            "community"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "party"
    },
    {
        "question": "He works for an international ............ that help poor people in Africa.",
        "choices": [
            "organisation",
            "cancer",
            "maker",
            "presentation"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "organisation"
    },
    {
        "question": "He is an experienced ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "biology",
            "biological",
            "biologically",
            "biologist"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "biologist"
    },
    {
        "question": "I don't have to do your homework; it's your ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "biography",
            "responsibility",
            "disease",
            "illness"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "responsibility"
    },
    {
        "question": "A good citizen has a ............ of duty.",
        "choices": [
            "skill",
            "sense",
            "responsibility",
            "charity"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "responsibility"
    },
    {
        "question": "If there is a ............ supermarket, we can shop easily.",
        "choices": [
            "really",
            "nearby",
            "nearly",
            "rarely"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "nearby"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Not all that glitters is gold\", this means you shouldn't be deceived by ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "appearance",
            "personality",
            "politeness",
            "character"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "appearance"
    },
    {
        "question": "He is really kind. He showed much ............ with my difficult situation.",
        "choices": [
            "empathy",
            "donation",
            "admiration",
            "charitable"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "empathy"
    },
    {
        "question": "She is a doctor. She works in the medical ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "transplant",
            "party",
            "field",
            "interview"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "field"
    },
    {
        "question": "Most patients are taken to the ............ hospital in our area.",
        "choices": [
            "local",
            "missing",
            "wild",
            "repeated"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "local"
    },
    {
        "question": "Winning the gold medal in the Olympics is a great ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "loss",
            "movement",
            "achievement",
            "organisation"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "achievement"
    },
    {
        "question": "A/An ............ is someone who is legally responsible for looking after someone or something.",
        "choices": [
            "biologist",
            "guardian",
            "hunter",
            "admirer"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "guardian"
    },
    {
        "question": "............ are animals such as cows and sheep that are kept on a farm.",
        "choices": [
            "livestock",
            "parties",
            "viewers",
            "guardians"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "livestock"
    },
    {
        "question": "To ............ is to carefully watch and check a situation in order to see how it changes or progresses over a period of time.",
        "choices": [
            "desire",
            "employ",
            "monitor",
            "transplant"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "monitor"
    }
]